## **PRAISE AYODELE**

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

### **PROFILE**

I am a dedicated and performance-driven software engineer with a pro-active approach to handling tasks. I have two years of experience working on client and server side architectures.

I am an effective team player offering extra-ordinary analytical skills and the important ability to think critically.

### **EXPERIENCE**

**FREELANCE | Lagos -** Fullstack developer February 2021 - PRESENT

- Building Consumer and Admin workflows, site reliability, and maintenance.
- Testing, Search engine optimization and ads control.

**FEELWARE Inc. | Lagos -** Fullstack developer intern March 2020 - February 2021

- Building, deploying an e-commerce client-side application with ReactJS consuming some REST API.
- Continuous refactoring of code to improve performance and readability.
- Server-side development with Node.js and Django.
- DBMS with MongoDB and PostgreSQL.

# **AERO CONTRACTORS | Lagos -** Technical intern July 2019 - Jan 2020

- Automated work orders, store orders, C-Checks and logistics.
- Led a team of 6 brilliant individuals to deliver projects ahead of schedule.
- Improved on the existing database model which reduced the accessibility time to significantly.

**Lagos, Nigeria** (+234) 901-400-7345

praise.t.ayodele@gmail.com praiseayodele.com

#### **SKILLS**

#### PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Python
- Javascript
- HTML, CSS
- Golang
- SQL

## **FRAMEWORKS**

- Django
- Node JS
- ReactJS

#### **TOOLS**

- Git
- Selenium
- Postgres
- Golang
- Mongodb
- Beautiful Soup
- Linux

## **EDUCATION**

**UNIVERSITY OF LAGOS** | Lagos, B.E. in Mechanical Engineering.

August 2015 - July 2021

## **VOLUNTEER WORK**

## REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH (HIV/AIDS) AWARENESS (CPET) | Nigeria

Currently a part of a team of enthusiastic young Nigerians desperate to impact society, my team and I routinely informs and creates awareness on sexually sensitive issues to improve lives.